Hello friends, how are you all?
Are you okay?  Today's video on our channel 360 Tamil
Investment is
Best Low Premium Health
Insurance Policy 2026.
Before going into the video, I have a
request for you.  If you need medical insurance, please
call the number on the screen on WhatsApp
.
In this video, we are going to look at eight policies
.  Superstar Essential Galaxy
Marvel, Ultimate Care Aditya Pir
Active 1 Next Nimopa Spire Gold
Variant Tata Medicare Select Manipal Signo Sarva Uttam
ICICI
Lambad Elevate All these eight policies are available in
this video and we can compare them. First, let's
see what
age you can take the policy for,
only Nimopa Aspire
has a maximum age limit of 65 years.  Even the average policy doesn't have that
much limit.  So you
can take it at any age.
Next, let's see how much insurance we can take
.
As for the coffee limit,
only Super Star Essence
is lacking.  The average plan has a lot of
coverage, so we
can take whatever we want.  There is a plan to take a maximum of one or two
crores
.
Next, we look at the room rent limit.
So this is very, very important.
Because depending on this room rent limit,
your claim will be greatly
affected.  So, if there
is no single private AC room available, it is
better to take a room with a private bathroom.   In
that sense, you have a
superstar plan.  Similarly, Tata
Medicare, ICICI, Lombard, Manipal,
Signal, Single AC Room, and
Depalta have also come.  There's
even a policy that says you can have a room if you want it
.
Come and select the policy you want.
Before you continue watching the video, I have
a request for you.  If
you haven't subscribed to this channel yet, please
subscribe.  Similarly,
press the bell button next to the notification to keep up with our videos.
Next, we come to see pre- and post-hospitalization
.  If a treatment
has been completed,
we would
have taken some scans and X-rays before the treatment.
It came and pre-hospitalized.  Similarly,
after the treatment is over,
the doctor will come back and
ask you to come back.
We'll tell you about the follow-up and post-hospitalization.  Let's see
how long it takes for this to arrive and how long it will be covered
.
Superstar is a bit lacking in terms of pre- and post-hospitalization
.  The middle plan also comes with
some coverage.  So, tell me
which one is best for you
.
Next is the no claim bonus.  This year,
we came here and wrote a policy.  If you
make a claim, you can come back next year and
make a little extra claim.
That's where the no claim bonus comes in.   In
that sense, the Super
Star Plan comes with a bonus of 50%
up to a maximum of 100% every year
.  If we take a policy of 7 lakhs or 10 lakhs, we will
get unlimited bonuses.  If you come to Galaxy and
don't claim, you can get 25% if you claim 100%, or if you
don't want this bonus,
you can even get a discount.  There is also an unlimited bonus of 50% and a maximum of 100% when you come to Ultimate Care
.  Aditya Birla has a maximum bonus of 500%
.
There is a maximum bonus of 300% when you come to Nivapala.  If
you take out a policy after the age of 46, you will not get any bonus.  You can get a
maximum bonus of 500% at Tata Medical
.  You can get a
maximum bonus of 1000% through the Manipal Simnala Rider
.  Similarly, with ICICI,
we can get a maximum bonus of 100%, or
even an unlimited bonus.   If
we take a prize of 10 lakh rupees,
then there is the same inflation
product rider.  If we take that,
our
insurance premiums will continue to rise in line with inflation
.
Next, the restore benefit means that if
we claim 2 lakhs on a 5 lakh rupee policy, then
the coverage of 5 lakh rupees will come back and
be restored in that same year.   We're going to
see if there's a limit to how often that happens.   When
you look at it that way, all
plans come with unlimited restore, and there are no
conditions like that.   So
even if the same person has the same illness,
we can still make a claim.  Ultimate
Care also comes with an unlimited auto recharge
booster.  So the recharge
is even 200%.
They have brought that kind of option in Ultimate Care.
Next, there is a waiting period for pre-existing diseases.
Now, if there are pre-existing diseases, such as high blood pressure,
sugar, cholesterol, or some other type of
surgery, we will have to undergo it.  This is all
coming from PET.   In
that sense, you can get the Super
Star plan with a three-year
waiting period, but you can get ABCD (
Asthma, Blood Pressure, Cholesterol, Diabetes) coverage and
Day One coverage
.  Similarly, there is a
three-year waiting period for Galaxy.
That waiting period
could be reduced to as little as 12 months.  There
is also the same ABCD rider.  Ultimate Care is the same
.  You can make a three-year waiting
period a waiting period
.
They also have an ABCD rider.  Aditya Birla has a
three-year waiting
period, a waiting period, and
all that kind of rider.  It seems like
all plans come with a waiting period and are a
hassle, but
I even got 30 days of coverage if I needed it
.  So,
come and select whatever suits you
.
Next, we will talk about Aruvi Chichi Specific Surgery
.  Kidney stones,
hernia, joint replacement,
ENT, cataract, piles, ulcers,
hernia,
and uterosacral removal are
only specific surgeries,
but we will come back to them at some point and
call them slow growth surgeries.   Let's
see what the waiting period is for this.
Looking at it that way, the
waiting list for specific surgery is only
two years after all plans have been implemented.  But
some plans come with the option to reduce it by a year
.
That means that Ultimate Care Galaxy Aditya
Birla has come to ICSC and has become an option
.
Next is coverage for the delivery of the newborn
In terms of delivery coverage,
only the Super Star plan rider
can get a maximum of one lakh rupees.  Similarly, in Ultimate Care,
we can claim a certain amount
.  Niva Bhupala has a 48-
month waiting period here.  A
maximum of one person can claim the insurance amount
.  Similarly, Tata
Medical can also be delivered for up to ₹1 lakh
.  This is the
rider who came.  It will
be like extra premium construction.  Wherever
we say rider optional, it seems like we have to
pay extra premium
.  Similarly, Manipal and ICICI
Bank have also come up with this option
.
Next, let's look at coverage for obesity treatment
.   When you
look at it that way, you get
this treatment, Galaxy,
Aditya Birla, ICC, Ambala, and
coverage.
Next,
let's see if there are any limitations to cataract treatment.   When you
look at it that way, you can't just
come up with a plan and set a
limit, saying, "We'll only give you this much."
So you can claim the actual amount
.
Next, come for a health checkup this year and
make a claim, then
come next year and get a health checkup
.  Some policies allow you to come in and get a
health checkup whenever you want through a rider
.  So let's see how that option comes along
.
Looking at it that way, we can
come and claim the Super Star Plan's specific test
.  This is the
rider who came.  Similarly, you can come to Galaxy and
claim a maximum of ₹20,000.
Depending on your insurance amount,
all plans, like Ultimate and Nivapa,
come with either a rider or an inbuilt rider
.
Next, let's look at the ambulance facility, that is, the coverage limit for using an ambulance in the event of an
emergency condition
.   When
you look at it that way, no
plan will come to the ambulance and
give you a limit.  So you can claim the actual amount
.
Next, if there is a situation where an air ambulance is unavoidable, such as
using an air ambulance,
then we can
come and see the coverage for that.
Looking at it that way, you can
claim up to 5 lakh rupees as a superstar
.  Harithbilla has
not received coverage for this.  You can come to Galaxy and
claim 10% of the insurance amount
.  Similarly, if you come across a similar plan,
you can claim up to the sum
insured through the ICICI rider, which is the sum insured for the Nivapala insurance policy and the Manipala insurance policy
.  You can get
coverage for this through Tata Medical and
get it through a rider.
Next, let's look at Siddha Unani Ayurveda and its
related treatment coverage
.
All plans can be
claimed as long as you come and get your coffee.
Next, we come to organ donor expenses, where we see if
someone donates an organ and
if so, we
see if there is a limit to the coverage for that.
Looking at it that way,
we can claim up to the amount we paid for all plans.
Next, let's talk about coverage for modern treatment,
i.e. advanced treatment
.
We are looking into whether there is a limit to this type of treatment, such as robotic surgery and chemotherapy.   When you
look at that wheel,
you can come and claim all the plans up to the insured amount
.
Next is domiciliary hospitalization, meaning that if
the situation is not such that you need to go to the hospital due to unavoidable circumstances, but the
hospital is not better, then you can
get treatment at home.
Coverage for that.
All plans come with coverage and
you can make a claim as long as you have taken out a copy.
Next is home care treatment.  I want to
get treatment from home.  That means you should
get treatment at the hospital.
But if we get some treatment at home for our convenience,
then there is
coverage for that.   In
that sense, some
superstars like Galaxy, Aditya
Birla, you have
coverage for this in Tata Medicare, Nivappa, ICI
.  There is no home care when you come here.
Nursing at home means that after the
treatment is over, a surgery is over, then after that,
nursing comes to the house and helps,
that is, giving those injections,
giving glucose, and doing this kind of assistant work,
then you
can come and get coverage for that.
Next, I will cover medical items like gloves,
masks, and sanitizers, and this will add
up to 20% to the treatment cost.  So, it's
very important to get coverage for this.   When you
look at it that way, it's like we get
this coverage through a rider in every plan
.
Next, we're going to look at the
premium lock.  This means that the
premium from health insurance will continue to rise
.  That's
something we know.  Maybe it would be
a bit difficult to make a claim if the premium was too high, so the
premium lock is the future that controls that to some extent.   In
that sense, Super
Star Plan Ultimate Care Galaxy Niva
Uppa has come here and has a future like this
.  If
we don't make a claim and the premium doesn't go up that much,
we
can't say that the premium will stay the same.
They can come and revise the premium whenever they want.  But don't
claim too much, otherwise you'll
see the extra benefit later.
All these plans are in this red color,
so if our rider
doesn't have the Extra Premium package, it will be
like making a slight change from the Premium Base Plan
.  So,
take it only if you need it.  If the premium weber comes to
Superstar and dies
due to an accident or if he has a
critical illness, there is no
need to pay the premium next year. If you
take our policy for five years and make any claim,
come in the sixth year and return the first year
premium.
Then, if you make a health booster for seven years,
then you will get the coverage for your phone and
increase it.
That's it. All of this comes with an inbuilt,
this red color is there. Everything
comes with an optional rider, so you
only need to take it if you need it.
The same goes for Galaxy.
They also give coverage for technology.
Similar to the NRI discount, you can also get a
discount through the wellness program
.  If
you watch Ultimate Girl, there
are some futures built in.
Health service, that is, that medicine, that kind of
discount, loyalty
boost, we have seen it before,
right? Health boost is the same, this is
loyalty boost, medi voucher, so the same kind of wellness
program, all this will be given.
Next, if you see Aditya Perlal, the
wellness program discount will be the same, HIV/AIDS coverage, mental
illness coverage, all this will be given.
Next, if you book a wellness
program,
you will get a discount.  Next, Tata came along and
everything was not inbuilt.
Everything comes and the rider just
takes what he needs.
Manipal too has come and everything is a rider.
Take it if you need it.
What discounts are available at IIC?
Everything else is just a rider.  If you need it,
take it.  This is what happens when our low
premium is like that, so take this rider and
this rider only if you need it
.  Because if we take all
this premium, our premium will keep going up
.
Next, let's look at the premium for the Rest of the World insurance for two adults and
two children aged 35 and over, which is 5 lakhs
.
All this premium came and
we only added one rider.  What is that, should
I say the payable item
or should I just include that?
Because if it doesn't come with a close
mask and sanitize, it will
be like putting 20% ​​on your hand when you get treatment.  So it's
better to just take that as our compulsory.
We have added it up in that way and
told them how much the premium would be.  So, come here and
select the plan that suits you best.   Please
tell me what you think in the comments.  If you liked this video, please like,
share, and subscribe.   To
claim copyright,
call the number on the screen on WhatsApp
.  Thank you, hello.